I changed my hair.
I haven't had this hair style for a
long time.
It's nostalgic.
I'm done.
I'm done with my hair.
Fluffy and fluffy.
It's normal.
Cake.
Cake refrigerator.
Water.
Corn.
I want to eat.
Please subscribe to this channel.
He thinks about one key.
but he doesn't know what it is.
Baby's favorite key
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching.
I'm going to the lobby of ZEPP Sapporo.
This is the place where everyone goes.
I was stretching here in the morning.
Do you go here?
I was stretching here in the hallway
last year.
I'm looking for a member.
What?
Can I touch this?
Ta-da!
I got this the other day.
I can take a picture with this.
This is it.
I can see Hitoka and Julia's
autographs.
All of them are here.
I'll go in from here.
Can I peek for 3 seconds?
Can I?
I hope they don't notice.
I'm nervous.
To be continued.
Why don't you notice?
You don't notice?
No one noticed me!
That's right… it was that guy!
Damn C'mon
Why don't you notice?
Why?
Isn't it strange?
Why don't you notice when there is
Hitoka?
Everyone, this is...
It seems to be distributed at the
entrance
I will read the QR
Newscast
Ah!
I got it!
This is the costume of this.
Not everyone can get this.
I got one of the costumes.
Can I do this?
What if I get the T-shirt?
I'll do it. What if I get it?
It's a three-part song.
Can I get this picture?
It's different from the hair accessory
I'm wearing now.
So cute!
Oh, the pictures are different for each
place.
It says, August 11th, the day before
Pia's birthday.
I think it's good to have a picture of
all three places.
Please try to do it at other places.
Thank you.
Let's do it again.
Let's go!
Do you trust us?
I'm glad you noticed.
That's all.
I played with ZEPP Sapporo's lobby.
I'll do my best in the second part.
Thank you for watching.
I'm sorry I'm covered with people.
Corn.
This is my favorite corn.
I wanted to eat corn tempura yesterday,
but I couldn't.
I like grilled corn.
Please eat.
So, look at this!
Today, we are going to the second part
of the concert in Hokkaido.
Oh, it's on.
I'll put it on.
It's scary.
I'll put it on here.
I can't say it.
Do you want to put it on here?
No, I don't want to.
I'm going to put it on my side.
Today's setlist.
The second song is called Red Heat.
Part 2.
Sideburns like the one I had when I was
in Red Heat.
But I didn't have a sense of taste at
that time.
It's been a while since I had a side
dish.
Matcha cake!
I wanna be a superstar!
Today, we're gonna do half-chewing-
chewing.
Side-pony!
We're gonna eat all the food we eat in
a week.
How many kilograms of hair do you have?
500g?
It's okay.
I think I have about 500g.
I ate all of them.
I ate soy sauce first, and then I
realized that soy sauce was really good.
Both of them were good.
It was super crispy.
It was crispy.
I enjoyed eating it.
I ate it, too.
I'm happy.
I'm in Hokkaido.
I wanna be in Hokkaido.
I'm going to make a new one.
What's going on?
Did you make a new one?
I'm going to make a new one.
I'm going to make a new heart for the
second part.
I'm going to make it three times during
the MC.
During the MC?
I think I can do it.
I couldn't wink 20 times.
When did you wink?
I think I winked three times.
I'm going to make a new one.
I'm going to wear twintails for the
second part.
I'm going to wear a cute hairstyle for
the first and second part.
Bye-bye!
I'm wearing twintails.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening in Hokkaido.
I love you, Chuu.
I'm wearing a turtleneck.
I forgot what I said.
What does it mean?
You were explaining it.
I forgot everything.
I forgot it.
The second part is called Dead Heat.
We are nervous.
We'll do our best.
It's been a while since we did Dead
Heat.
Let's show it to the people in
Hokkaido.
Let's do it.
Please look forward to the next
episode!
Honey!
I'm worried about my heart
I tried to be a little more popular
I'm a little more popular
I'll do my best
I'm Kageyama, and I'm a Kageyama-chan
How do you feel?
I feel like an announcer
You don't bite at all?
I don't bite
I'm Kageyama, and this is my first
Kageyama-chan tour
I'm Kageyama-chan
I'm Ilya-chan
Thank you for coming to the Heartget
Tour 2022,
that was where you resurred in Tokyo in
the summer.
Before we start, I would like to ask
the audience to be careful.
We will not allow you to take pictures,
record, or record in the venue.
The audience in the front seats cannot
stand up and watch.
Please sit down and watch.
I'm sorry.
Now, we will start the show.
Hokkaido is a little cold, but let's
make a hot live together.
Please look forward to it.
Please wait a little longer.
Ready, set, go!
Rock on!
Yes.
Good girl.
OK, now ready...
Oops.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Thank you for watching!
I can't help it, so goodbye
The important things are always by my
side
They overflowed so much that I couldn't
see them
The first page I wrote
The night sky, the shooting stars, the
glittering sky
I'm still alive, climbing those hills
We ran, laughing together
Someday, your voice will...
Thank you very much!
Bye bye!
Thank you for your hard work!
Say bye bye!
Good job! It was fun!
I think I did too much.
It was fun.
Good job!
Fabri, you are fighting against the
camera.
I'm glad that everyone was waving their
hands.
Thank you.
It was fun.
Everyone was kind.
It was cold in the airport.
This live was too hot.
It was cold.
I couldn't hold back my sweat.
Thank you for the people in Hokkaido
who came to see us.
Thank you.
Thank you, Tamashii.
Good job!
Thank you.
We met Kurumi-chan for the first time
at the Sapporo Park.
She was so cute.
When I was at the Tokyo Dome, I was
there and I saw Kurumi-chan.
I was surprised.
She was in front of me and she was
facing me.
She was so close to me.
Kurumi-chan is close to you.
Yes, she was so cute.
She was so cute.
I was so surprised.
I was surprised.
She was so cute.
It's always special and I think it's a
great tour.
It was fun.
Thank you very much.
Everyone, take your time.
That's right.
It's over.
Thank you very much.
I love this.
I've been looking forward to coming
here.
I'm so happy.
This is the second time in my life.
This is the second time in a live show.
It's twice in total.
I don't know what to say.
I'm sure the audience will be happy,
too.
I want to show it to everyone.
I want to do it in summer.
We'll do something like a special
house.
We'll do it in summer.
It's going to be a great concert.
It's not going to be a concert.
That's right.
I thought about the hair style of the
members of Hokkaido.
How did you like it?
How was it?
It's a summer-like style.
It was fun.
It's a little new.
It's a little different from usual.
I've been thinking about Hiori's hair
for a while.
I've been thinking about it since I was
told two weeks ago.
It's too early to think about it.
I've been thinking about it for a
while.
It was cute.
Everyone was cute.
It was really cute.
The concert is over.
This is the last concert.
I'll be back in a few hours.
I've never done it before.
I'll be back.
I'll be back tomorrow.
I'm here, so it's okay.
Please clap your hands and leave a
comment.
Bye bye!
Wow!
What is that?
It's a letter!
Wow!
The first time they've seen a letter!
I want to give the best excitement to
as many people as possible.
I want to step up to the tour through
this Makuhari Messe.
I want to improve my performance so
that I can live a good live and not lose
to this venue.
I'm really looking forward to seeing
the smiles of the young people.
I want to make a lot of memories.
I think it would be fun if the six of
us could go to various places.
October 22nd is...
Let's go!
Dokusen Makuhari!
I'm waiting!
Don't miss the next video!
Please subscribe to the channel!
I'm sure if I laugh, the world will
shine
I can turn my umbrella around and relax
If I don't do that, I can't walk
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I want to share my feelings
The scenery I don't know is still in
front of me
Hey, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
On the canvas of a damaged heart
I'll draw a fragment of the future
It will guide me
I can say it now, the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I remember right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a flower, the tears
are overflowing
I wear a rainbow dress